练习 1-31：被挤掉的音节。语调也可以完全去掉
Exercise 1-31, Squeezed out syllables. Intonation can also completely get rid of
某些完整音节。有些重音在第一个音节的较长单词，
certain entire syllables. Some longer words that are stressed on the first
会把弱音节直接挤掉。遮住常规拼写，只读这些
syllable squeeze weak syllables right out. Cover up the regular spelling and read the
phonetics. Accidentally, Actually, Aspirin, Average, Bakery, Basically,
Beverage, Boundary, Broccoli, Business, cabinet,
camera, catholic, chocolate, comfortable, conference, corporal, coverage, desperate,
diamond,
diaper, different, emerald, emery, every, family, favorite, finally, general,
groceries,
history, interest, jewelry, liberal, mathematics, memory, natural, Niagara,
nursery, onion, opera, orange, preference, probably,
realize, restaurant, separate, several, theory, threatening, vegetable, victory.